<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Sumita Mukund</title>
    <link>https://sumitii.github.io/personal-site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Sumita Mukund</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 21:02:18 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sumitii.github.io/personal-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creative Works</title>
      <link>https://sumitii.github.io/personal-site/work/creative/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 21:02:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sumitii.github.io/personal-site/work/creative/</guid>
      <description>Creative Endeavors Writing, public speaking, and the intersection of technology and pop culture have always been passions of mine. Below are some my creative endeavors.
Writing A College Essay AKA an Ode to Dunkin&#39; Donuts
Speaking Engagements How Reality TV Inspired me to Learn UX
Donut JS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sudarsna Mukund</title>
      <link>https://sumitii.github.io/personal-site/work/wild-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 21:02:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sumitii.github.io/personal-site/work/wild-zoo/</guid>
      <description>The Wild Zoo A graduate prototyping project for Drexel University&amp;rsquo;s CCI Master&amp;rsquo;s Program Product Description The Wild Zoo mobile application is ideally designed to allow parents to easily schedule and purchase online tickets for exhibits, events, and other fun activities with the family. In addition, it provides easy access to admission information, parking availability, and resources for trip planning. Integrated features such as QR codes for simple access to the Zoo, imagery support, color enhancements, font clarity, and button visibility to allow a healthy user experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Soup</title>
      <link>https://sumitii.github.io/personal-site/work/tigersoup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 21:02:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sumitii.github.io/personal-site/work/tigersoup/</guid>
      <description>TigerSoup When change comes to an industry, marketing people tend to follow their tried and true methods. As the rules of the game change, it is imperative to think outside the box in order to create successful outcomes for clients. Tiger Soup assembles custom remote teams of creative leaders to solve unique marketing challenges that current resources cannot solve either through lack of available time or lack of experience.
Working with the team at Amplified by Design, and Amsterdam-based illustrator Katsiaryna Dubovik I took on the role of both experience designer and web developer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
